<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Positivity News</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Positivity News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://positivity-news.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Positivity News Issue 5</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/06/05/Positivity-News-Issue-5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/06/05/Positivity-News-Issue-5/</guid><description>Landmark EMS June 5, 2020 Issue 5
o P s (^) i t (^) v
i e w y t i N s We wanted to inform you all that we will be continuing Positivity News throughout the summer. We are hoping to
keep the Enrichment Google Classroom up during the summer. We can continue to post new editions in your
Enrichment Classroom every month. Please keep sending me or Ms.</description></item><item><title>Positivity News Issue 4</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/30/Positivity-News-Issue-4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/30/Positivity-News-Issue-4/</guid><description>Landmark EMS May 30, 2020 Issue 4 The Positivity News Editors: Mitchell Geffin, Ms. DeJoy and Mrs. Ellis Please submit any POSITIVITY NEWS about you or your community for the last issue by: June 1
Welcome to the 4th issue of Positivity News. Thank you Landmark community for sending me optimistic news!! Thank you to Mrs. Ellis and Ms. DeJoy for helping me with Positivity News!! Spread as much positivity as you can during these challenging times!</description></item><item><title>Positivity News Issue 3</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/16/Positivity-News-Issue-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/16/Positivity-News-Issue-3/</guid><description>Landmark EMS May 16, 2020 Issue 3 The Positivity News Editors: Mitchell Geffin, Ms. DeJoy and Mrs. Ellis Please submit any POSITIVITY NEWS about you or your community for the next issue by: May 25
Welcome to the 3rd issue of Positivity News! Thank you to the people who send me positive stories and thank you for the incredible support. Thank you also to Mrs. Ellis and Ms. DeJoy for helping me!</description></item><item><title>Postivity News Issue 2.5</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/07/Positivity-News-Issue-2.5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/07/Positivity-News-Issue-2.5/</guid><description>We are very grateful and thankful to the faculty and students that sent us uplifting
articles. Unfortunately, this is the final issue of the year, so we hope you have an
amazing summer. Remember to not let the negativity over rule you.
The Positivity News Club The InterCultural Group gathered together for their last meeting. We had special alumni
visitors, Ethan, Nathaniel and Landon, who shared impactful advice and celebrated our</description></item><item><title>Positivity News Issue 2</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/Postivity-News-Issue-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/05/Postivity-News-Issue-2/</guid><description>Edition 2 Landmark EMS May 2, 2020 Issue 2 The Positivity News Editors: Mitchell Geffin, Ms. DeJoy and Mrs. Ellis Please submit any POSITIVE NEWS about you or your community for the next issue by: May 11 Mrs. Robinson and her daughter helped their friend
celebrate her 13th birthday by
driving by her house and
honking their horns along with
many others. Also they called
out the window and wished</description></item><item><title>Postivity News Issue 1</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/04/Positivity-New-Issue-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/2020/04/Positivity-New-Issue-1/</guid><description>Landmark EMS April 2020 Issue 1
The Positivity News Editors: Mitchell Geffin, Ms. DeJoy and Mrs. Ellis Welcome to the first issue of The Positivity News! We are excited to share some of the many POSITIVE stories that occur in the Landmark EMS community. These events are told by the Landmark students and staff. We hope these accounts of kindness and positivity remind you of the good that is happening in our community and how much you all contribute to it.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/archive/</guid><description>the collection of old posts</description></item><item><title>Test</title><link>https://positivity-news.github.io/post/test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://positivity-news.github.io/post/test/</guid><description>test</description></item></channel></rss>